Olha Afanasieva Front-end developer



Phone: +4560567160

Address: Copenhagen, 2300

Email: afanasievaolja@gmail.com

Residence permit with right to work

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/olha-afanasieva/

PROFILE

Enthusiastic and highly motivated front-end developer with experience in creating websites supporting different browsers and mobile devices. Implementation of responsive design, writing code from scratch and trying to develop the best possible web-solutions. I also have a keen eye on new technologies and include them into my projects.

EXPERIENCE

Jan 2020 – now, Front-end Developer Internship at Whyser.

Developing a single-page application - platform for creating powerful and engaging strategies. Delivering design based on UI theme, implementing functionality using Vue.js.

Aug 2019 – Dec 2019, Front-end Developer Internship at CareerToGo.

Developing a single-page application – career app, using Vue.js and Vuetify. Extending web-application to desktop version, implementing new design.

2012 – 2018, accompanying spouse.

Relocating to different countries (Poland, Denmark), learning different cultures and languages. Taking care of my family. Keeping up to date with new technologies in software development.

<u>July 2010 – Sep 2011, content manager, IT-tour (tour search and booking system), Kharkiv, Ukraine.</u>

Maintaining a high volume of data. Monitoring the company's crawlers, identification of system errors. Systematization of information and its reduction to a single form.

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

HTML:

CSS3/SCSS:

JavaScript:

JQuery:

Vue.js:

React:

• • • • • • •

Other technologies and tools I had opportunity to work with:

AdobeXD Bootstrap Git

Visual Code Photoshop

TypeScript Figma Vuetify

PORTFOLIO

olkaa.github.io/

GITHUB

github.com/OlkaA

LANGUAGES

Danish: Beginner
English: Fluent
Ukrainian: Native
Russian: Native
Polish: Beginner

REFERENCES

References available on request.

EDUCATION

Aug 2019 – Jan 2020, student in Hack Your Future - full-stack software developer, Copenhagen, Denmark.

Learning HTML, CSS, JavaScript, MySql, NodeJS, React along with completing and solving different projects each week of the course.

<u>2009 – 2010, Master's degree in computer engineering.</u> Engineer-researcher of computer systems and networks. Kharkiv National University of Radioelectronics, Kharkiv, Ukraine.

Master thesis project: Methods of developing a web interface for building corporate informational systems.

<u>2005 – 2009, Bachelor's degree in computer engineering.</u> Kharkiv National University of Radioelectronics, Kharkiv, Ukraine.

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

<u>Feb 2019 – now, support mentor in HYF</u> - Supporting students by reviewing their homework, giving feedback.

<u>Nov 2019, GOTO Copenhagen</u> - Provided physical and logistical support to presenters and event attendees. Had an opportunity to learn from group of the brightest minds in tech and business about China's technostrategic ambitions, introduction to Quantum Computing, advices from Apple Cofounder, how to use HTML properly to make sites that work better, faster and include more people.